roblav96@gmail.com



401-203-3195



New York, NY



Altruistic, ego-free, humble, open-minded



Leader, openly criticize, will take charge

Eager to learn, more eager



"If you want to go far, go



Public seminar speaker & event attendee



+2,000 GitHub contributions yearly



TypeScript



Node.js

React.js

to teach

together"





Vue.js



Amazon Web Services



Serverless



Redis



PostgreSQL



MongoDB



Google Analytics Terminal / Bash



Electron



NativeScript



Sublime Text

Robert Laverty

Full-Stack Software Engineer





README.md

I'm a Problem Solver. That statement can easily be validated by the numerous projects I've created from the ground up. Every project was developed because of a problem I had experienced myself. I've taken them from an idea, all the way to a minimum viable product and talking to investors. Throughout these endeavors I've learned how to efficiently identify a problem, produce a solution based on meaningful metrics, analytics, and A/B tests, market and sell the product, then scale to a larger audience. I want to put my extraordinary skill-sets to good use at your company and work with a team of your best innovators. Please don't hesitate to contact me if you have any questions. Thank you!

Experience



<u>CrowdPass</u> - Lead Software Engineer

Jan 2023 - Oct 2023



access system, then deployed to events hosted by Lamborghini, Ecolab, and Palm Springs Surf

Designed and built the frontend, backend, and mobile app for an RFID+NFC wristband entry



May 2022 - Dec 2022

Built the entire frontend from the ground up, precisely following a Figma design















Sep 2018 - Feb 2022



Futon Media - Creator

Instantly stream Movies and TV Shows via Emby Media









<u>LeverEdge</u> - Lead Software Engineer









Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

Upgraded frontend to use Nuxt.js, created a LinkedIn scraper with headless Puppeteer













May 2019 - Oct 2019

Sep 2018 - Apr 2019

Dec 2016 - Aug 2018

Scaled product, integrated analytics/metrics, upgraded frontend to use TypeScript









<u>DocHub</u> - Lead Software Engineer















<u>Kava Labs</u> - Senior Full-Stack Software Engineer



Robinhood Tools - Creator Advanced tools and resources for trading equities on Robinhood















TS N 🛊 🖷 🕀 🕼 🐧 📦 S 🌗

Sep 2016 - Aug 2017





EMC Corporation - Full-Stack Software Engineer

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015

Helped develop scanner reporting front-end in an agile environment using scrum methodologies









Education



Google Primer - Grow With Google Program

Insights from trusted industry experts insights from trusted industry experts into jargon-free interactive lessons featuring practical next steps for reaching your business or career goals



University of Rhode Island - Computer Science

Voluntarily resigned due to financial constraints

Sep 2009 - June 2010